{
  "extraDescription": "each operand is in 6-12",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "7 + 12",
      "answer": "19"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 7",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 8",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 7",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 8",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 12",
      "answer": "22"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 7",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 7",
      "answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 7",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 9",
      "answer": "21"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 8",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 8",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 11",
      "answer": "22"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 10",
      "answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 11",
      "answer": "23"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 10",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 9",
      "answer": "19"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 6",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 11",
      "answer": "21"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 9",
      "answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 11",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 10",
      "answer": "19"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 11",
      "answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 12",
      "answer": "21"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 7",
      "answer": "19"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 10",
      "answer": "22"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 10",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 11",
      "answer": "19"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 6",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 9",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 7",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 6",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 9",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 9",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 6",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 9",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 10",
      "answer": "21"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 8",
      "answer": "19"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 10",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 8",
      "answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 12",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 12",
      "answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 6",
      "answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 11",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 12",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 6",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 12",
      "answer": "23"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 6",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 8",
      "answer": "16"
    }
  ]
}
